[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All planets, comets and asteroids orbit around the Sun.  What percentage of the Solar Systems mass does the Sun account for?", "correct_answer": "99.8%", "incorrect_answers": ["around one-half", "86.2%", "around 10%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is wrong about the Glass frogs from the amphibian family Centrolenidae?", "correct_answer": "They are found mainly in Australia and Tasmania.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are arboreal animals.", "All of these", "Their skin is transparent."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Japanese version of chess known as?", "correct_answer": "shogi", "incorrect_answers": ["kyoki", "shatranj", "masala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This densely populated valley in the state of Utah is enclosed by steep mountains in every direction except the northwest.", "correct_answer": "Salt Lake Valley", "incorrect_answers": ["St. Lawrence Valley", "Livermore Valley", "Las Vegas Valley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the cartoon cat that terrorizes the mouse, Jerry?", "correct_answer": "Tom", "incorrect_answers": ["Gat", "Cat", "Gus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What essential vitamin is supplied through the consumption of carrots?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin A", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin K", "Vitamin D", "Vitamin E"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The leopard, lion and the tiger appear in this variation of chess.", "correct_answer": "Dou Shou Qi", "incorrect_answers": ["chaturanga", "shatranj", "makruk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how long is a lions gestation period?", "correct_answer": "120 days", "incorrect_answers": ["200 days", "30 days", "60 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a Japanese dish made from thinly sliced, pickled ginger which is kept in a solution of sugar and water.", "correct_answer": "Gari", "incorrect_answers": ["Shiokara", "Natto", "Kapi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Dinotopia, the fictional place where humans and dinosaurs live together in James Gurneys books and Hallmarks mini series?", "correct_answer": "A hidden island", "incorrect_answers": ["A planet", "A mountain", "A large volcano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An overdose of what vitamin can cause diarrhea, nausea and heartburn?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B5", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin A", "Vitamin K", "Vitamin C"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film, set in 1930s Louisiana, was adapted from a novel of the same name and directed by Frank Darabont.", "correct_answer": "The Green Mile", "incorrect_answers": ["American Beauty", "Boys Dont Cry", "The End of the Affair"]}]